Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Program production files
  - Production files, by show title, 447 folders
    - Tishomingo Blues: The Story of Composer Spencer Williams, 1999; 2 folders; 1 computer disk (Box 126)
    - Tommy Saunders Midwest All Stars: Runnin' Wild, 2001; 1 folder (Box 126)
    - Three-Trumpet Salute to Louis Armstrong, 2001; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Tio Family: A New Orleans Clarinet Dynasty, 2005; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Tin Roof Blues: The Story Of The New Orleans Rhythm Kings, 1999; 2 folders; 5 computer discs (Box 127)
    - Treat It Gentle: The Sidney Bechet Story, 1998; 2 folders; 1 computer disk (Box 127)
    - Tribute to the Original Dixieland Jazz Band, Live From the Stanford Jazz Workshop, 1997; 1 folder (Box 127)
    - Triple Crown of Tunesmiths, A: Youmans, Barris and Green, 2008-10-23; 1 folder (Box 91)
    - Two of a Kind: Swinging Duos at The Landing, 2008; 1 folder (Box 127)
    - Turk and Lu: West Coast Classic Jazz in Concert, 2009; 1 folder (Box 127)
    - Turk and Lu: West Coast Giants of Jazz, 1996; 1 folder; 1 computer disk (Box 127)
    - Under a Southern Moon: Blues Queens and Tent Shows, 2005; 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Unsung Genius of Kenny Davern: A Jazz Appreciation Month Special, 2011; 1 folder (Box 127)
    - Unsung Songwriters: The Great Craftsmen, 1 folder (Box 128)
    - W.C., James P., and Bessie: The Geography of Jazz, 2002; 2 folders (Box 128)
    - West Coast Classic Jazz: A Tribute to Turk Murphy and Lu Waters, 1993; 1 folder; 4 compuiter disks (Box 128)
    - What Are You Doin' New Year's Eve?, 1994-2010; 1 folder (Box 128)
    - When Swing Was the Thing: Diary of a Swing Era Teen, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 128)
    - When I Grow Too Old to Dream: The Memories of Danny Barker, 2006; 1 folder (Box 128)
    - Whiz-Kid of Swing: The Story of Pioneering Record Producer John Hammond, 2006; 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Wild Fiddler from Phillie: Joe Venuti and His Jazz Violin, 1993-1999; 2 folders; 2 computer disks (Box 128)
    - Wild Man Blues: The Eccentric Genius of Jelly Roll Morton, 2003; 2 folders; 2 computer disks (Box 128)
    - William Gottlieb's Golden Age of Jazz, 2001; 3 folders (Box 129)
    - Wishing on the Moon: Riverwalk Crooners in Concert, 2001; 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Woman's Touch: Celebrating Women Composers in Jazz, 2007; 7 folders (Box 129)
    - Women of the Harlem Renaissance, 2008; 2 folders (Box 129)
    - World on Seven Strings: The Life of Jazz Guitar Master Bucky Pizzarelli, 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Wrap Your Cares in Rhythm: A concert of Recession-Proof Tunes, 2009; 1 folder (Box 129)
    - Yank Lawson and Bob Haggart: Swinging with The Bob Cats, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 129)
    - Zoot and Al: The Brotherhood of Prez, 2003; 1 folder (Box 129)
  - 2006 Recording Sessions [scripts and rundowns], 2005-2006; 12 folders (Box 223)
  - Black History Month Shows, 9 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 188)
  - Compositions and Recordings Binder, 1 folder (Box 142)
  - DAT Library, 1991-1998; 1 folder (Box 140)
  - Master Show List 270, 2005; 1 folder (Box 140)
  - Master Tape Inventory, DAT Lending Schedule, 1 folder; 2 computer disks (Box 140)
  - Master Tune List Binder, 1 folder (Box 140)
  - Rerun Productions, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 140)
  - Rundown Binder A-J; K-Z [should replicate digital files on hard drive], 2 folders (Box 141)
  - Rundowns, 2009-2011; 1 folder (Box 142)
  - Rundowns, 2012; 1 folder (Box 142)
  - Scripts, 2003-2011; 219 folders
    Each folder holds material from a recording session date, including agendas, correspondence, rundowns, and CD-R recordings consisting of drafts, promotional and fundraising spots, voiceovers, etc. Some spots were intended for specific radio stations. There are also older and and newer scripts in the folders, as well as new voiceovers for rebroadcasts. Original chronological order has been retained.
    - 5/12/2003 - 2/12/2004, 17 folders; 25 CD-Rs (Box 143)
    - 2/18/2004 - 12/9/2004, 16 folders; 27 CD-Rs (Box 144)
    - 12/22/2004 - 11/1/2005, 20 folders; 26 CD-Rs (Box 145)
    - 11/5/2005 - 8/22/2006, 18 folders; 24 CD-Rs (Box 146)
    - 8/22/2006 - 1/18/2007, 16 folders; 2 CD-Rs (Box 147)
    - 1/19/2007 - 5/3/2007, 9 folders; 5 CD-Rs (Box 148)
    - 6/4/2007 - 10/30/2007, 19 folders; 3 CD-Rs (Box 149)
    - 11/8/2007 - 3/26/2008, 16 folders (Box 150)
    - 3/27/2008 - 9/18/2008, 14 folders; 2 CD-Rs (Box 151)
    - 9/18/2008 - 3/9/2009, 18 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 152)
    - 3/17/2009 - 1/19/2010, 20 folders; 2 CD-Rs (Box 153)
    - 12/22/2009 - 10/6/2010, 24 folders (Box 154)
    - 11/17/2000 - 5/11/2011, 12 folders; 1 CD-R (Box 155)
  - Shows, 1989-2000; 2 folders (Box 140)
  - Tune and Show Lists Binder, 3 folders (Box 140)
    Unused Tunes 5/15/2002; Show List Thru #199; [tune list] Revised 11/28/2001
- Program production recording elements
  Miscellaneous promos, spots, tags, samples, segments, voiceovers (VOs), outtakes (outs), fundraisers, etc. Arranged in chronological order according to medium. None are explicitly tied to a specific program, although some were used for muliple programs.
  - Production Elements, CD-R
    - Misc. Production Elements, CD-R, 2006-2011; 120 CD-Rs (Audio 89, Audio 130)
      Voiceovers, pickups, spots, etc. from binder labeled "Interviews and Voicetracks, David, Vernell, Jim." 2006-2009 in Box 89. 2010-2011 in Box 130.
    - Website on Disk RW Landing and Backup, 2001-09-14; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - New Riverwalk Credits, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: January, February, March; April, May June; July, August, September, 2002; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - Promos for Session, 2002-01-25; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - Applause and Ambience at the Landing, 2002-03-20; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - David Holt Promos, 2002-08-13; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Louis Armstrong Premium Spots, 2002-09; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Kilgore/Riverwalk Anniversary Spots, 2002-09-06; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Brendan Fraser VO, 2002-09-10; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos, 2002-10-01; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - Promos, 2002-10; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos, 2002-12 - 2003-01; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Fundraising Testimonials Master, 2003-01-16; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - JCJB Riverwalk Jazz Sampler for Arbor Records, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - JCJB With Neill Walsdorf. A Hot Jazz Clarinet Tribute Live at the Landing, 2005-05-12; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: January, February, March, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - David Holt, 2003-01-14; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - Bix CD - Tunes Not In Order, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos, 2003-02; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - RW Alternate Openings. Landmarks; Pres and Lady, 2003-02-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - New Credits, 2003-02-10; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Riverwalk On The Road Unedited VO, 2003-02-24; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - RW11 David Holt VO, 2003-02-26; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos, 2003-03; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - RW15 Blues Legends, 2003-03-12; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - Brown Foundation Tags, 2003-03-25; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - RW 17 Spring Fever Vox, 2003-03-25; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: April, May, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Women Blues RW20 Promos, 2003-04-08; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos, 2003-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Nightspell, 2003-05-21; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promo: June-October. Rough Tracks, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: November, December, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - String of Pearls. For Our Dear Friends Toby and Barnie O'Connor, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: January-April, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: May, June, July, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: August, September, 2004; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - From The Heart, 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: January-April, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Arlen PRI Specials, 2005-03; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Spring Fundraiser Premium. From The Heart: Louis Armstrong Remembers, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Voice of God and Nightspell Intros, 2005-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Backup Original Pieces, 2005-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Joe Gwathmey Riverwalk Opens, 2005-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Promos: May-August, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Vernell, David VOs, 2007-10-08; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - VIP Promo Book, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - 5 Pieces by Jim Cullum, 2008-05-13; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - PRPD Sampler, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Jazz Centennial Segments, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Edu Video Teaser - Pub Domain Tunes, 2010-02-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - undated CD-R elements
      - Carver Clips, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Dick Hyman, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Dick Hyman, Jersey Lightning Mixes, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 87)
      - Jim's Spots [KCSM, KSTX, WUSFG, etc.], 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Keith Harter Music, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Long Way...Sutton Promo; Armstrong Man / World Promo, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - misc VOs, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Nightspell Edits, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 87)
      - PRI Radio Promos Rebecca Kilgore, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Leon Redbone Samples, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Roll Em Pete, 2 Versions, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Royal Garden Blues; Goose Pimples, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - RW 52 Playing Favorites Promos, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Various Landing Applause, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - Vernel Recording Session Riverboat?, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
      - WKCC Spots, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
  - Production Elements, DAT
    - Make Me A Pallet On The Floor. Tune Not Used in Brass Bands Show, 1 DAT (Audio 79)
    - Misc. DAT Edit Parts, Promos, Back-ups (Modules/Parts, Tags, Ambience/Applause, Credits, IDs, etc.), 55 DATs (Audio 51)
    - Misc. DATs "from Upstream 2000" [pick-ups, promos, voiceovers, demos, production parts, etc.], 1995-2000; 48 DATs (Audio 50)
    - RW Safety. All Takes, 2000-02-03; 1 DAT (Audio 79)
    - Voice Tracks #1, 2000-01 - 2001-04-17; 50.0 DATs (Audio 45)
    - Voice Tracks #2, 2001-04-23 - 2002-11-19; 48 DATs (Audio 46)
    - RW #15 Vox Trax, 2003-03-11; 1 DAT (Audio 79)
    - New Joe Gwathmey Introductions, 2003-05; 1 DAT (Audio 79)
    - Promo Spots, DAT
      - Promos 1, 1991-1999; 40 DATs (Audio 47)
      - Promos 2, 1999-2002; 40 DATs (Audio 48)
      - Promos 3, 2001-2003; 14 DATs (Audio 49)
  - Production Elements, Tape (Reel)
    - A [unidentified], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Bobby Hackett/Jelly Roll Morton Show Reel, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - From "You Were Never Lovelier", 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - I'm Old Fashioned. Dialogue/M. Pick. 1st Show (Hardman Prod.), 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - Joe Williams, "Who She Do" (Extra Song); Sax Show, "Spain", 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Misc. Blues, Texas Roots, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - New Year's Eve Extra Song, "Big Noise", 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Open Cuts, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Benny Goodman/Boogie Woogie/David Holt - Helen Ward Interview, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Blues/King Oliver/West Coast Classics, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Bob Wilber/Clark Terry-Basie Years, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Boogie Woogie, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Boogie Woogie/Fats Waller/Benny Carter/Bob Wilber, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Earl Hines/Hoagy Carmichael/Benny Carter/Fats Waller, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Hoagy, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - Outs: Hot Bands/KC Big Blues/Bechet/Ladies/Hampton-New Year's, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Jelly Roll, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: JCJB, David Holt Misc., 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Misc. Anniversary Show/Bobby Hackett/Joe Williams, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Misc. New Years/Anniversary Show, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 19)
    - Outs: Sedge. Sendak, Angell, LeGuin, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
    - Production Elements 1-6A, 6B-12 Dolby A NR [1991?], 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
    - Promo Slates, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - Wizard of Oz, Gershwin on The Man I Love/M. Pick (Hardman Prod.), 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - APR Logo, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - APR Logo, 1987-11-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - APR Logo, 1990-05-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - Joe Gwathmey. Playback?, 1990; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
      In 1983, following a period of financial crisis for NPR, Gwathmey was named vice president in charge of programming and played an instrumental role in rebuilding NPR's program services. Within two years NPR's programming had become more extensive and diverse than ever before, winning numerous prestigious awards for production and journalistic excellence.
      Gwathmey's return to Texas was prompted by the opportunity to bring NPR programming to listeners in the last large market in the country not served by an NPR-affiliated radio station. Following his departure from NPR in Washington, D.C., Gwathmey was honored by the Corporation for Public Broadcasting with the prestigious Edward R. Murrow Award, public radio's highest honor.
      Upon his arrival in San Antonio in 1988 Gwathmey became the manager of classical music station KPAC-FM and helped in the final push to put NPR member station KSTX-FM on the air. He also guided a restructuring of the parent organizations licensed to operate KPAC and KSTX that resulted in the creation of the new non-profit corporation, Texas Public Radio. In 1989 he initiated plans that led to a major increase in KPAC's transmission power and to the construction of new studio and office facilities in 1992.
    - Riverwalk Demo. Safety Master, 1990-03-12; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Misc. Crowd Reaction/Ambience, 1990-07-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
    - Riverwalk Demo, 1991; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Promos - Product Promotion/Hyatt Credit, 1991; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Riverwalk Extra Cuts. Dick Hyman/John Sheridan - Nobody Knows When You're Down and Out, 1992; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Riverwalk '93 Extra Songs, 1993; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 7)
      1. King Oliver Show - Too Late 2. West Coast Classics - Antigua Blues 3. West Coast Classics - Terrible Blues 4. W.C. Handy - Yellow Dog Blues, with intro NG 5. After Hours Stein and Grosz - Dardanella NG 6. After Hours Stein and Grosz - China Boy NG
    - After Hours. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (Based), 1993; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
    - Riverwalk Promo Music, 1993-1994; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 9)
    - Riverwalk Extra Songs, 1994; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 12)
    - 92nd St. Y Playback Master. PRI Open and Count; Tin Roof Blues; Jelly Roll Morton VO, 1994; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 12)
    - Playback Master Transfers. Doin' The New Low Down; Santa Claus Blues; Promo, Closing Credits: Christmas Show; Closing Credits: Battle of Bands Show, 1994; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 9)
    - Ellington - Clark Terry. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-08-05; 2 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Porgy and Bess Pt 1and2 Outs, 1994-08-30; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 11)
    - N.Y., Christmas Remixes, 1994-10-31; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 12)
    - Prez and Lady Day, Louie in the Thirties Playback Master, 1995-02-04; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 13)
    - Bix and Hoagy/Trombone/Boogie Woogie Playback Master. Historic Recordings, 1994-1995; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 14)
    - Nightspell W/Evan, 1996; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 16)
    - Transfer Reel. Harlem Rhapsody; Lenox to Broadway; The Gospel in Jazz, 1996; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 16)
    - Harlem Rhapsody, Gershwin and Gershwin Playback Master, 1996-03-25; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 17)
  - Production Elements, Tape (Cassette)
    - Assorted Business. Handy, Venuti, Jam, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Black History Promo, Andy Razaf, 1999; 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Riverwalk - Blues. New Open, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Brian Gillespie - Bix Audition, 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - Lena Horne, Jim Cullum Promo Spots, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - JCJB Symphony. A La Bauduc. Symphony, First Movement [unidentified recording from Playing with Fire], 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - New Nightspell Versions, 2003-07-16; 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Riverwalk Business, 1993-01-26; 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Riverwalk Spots, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - [Still Breathing] Lou Rawls, Brendon Fraser Promo Celebrity Spots, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - [Still Breathing] Joanna Going, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - [Still Breathing] Brendan Fraser, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Still Breathing Playback Choices, 1996-05-25; 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Jerry Stiller as Condon, 1 audiocassette (Audio 136)
    - Cory Walter Voice Demo, 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
- Program research files
  Historical background information from a variety of sources, including Rutgers' Institute of Jazz Studies, the Hogan Jazz Archives at Tulane University, the Vincent Voice Library at Michigan State, and from private collectors and researchers. Material in in most cases consists of photocopied articles, book chapters, and press kits. See also program research recordings, biographical files, and program concept files.
  General/misc. files also include show ideas, scripts, and bibliographies from the program web page.
  - Research files - miscellaneous and general
    - Academy Award Winning Songs, 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Albert, Don / South West Territory Bands / Jazz in San Antonio [Carver show], 7 folders (Box 181)
      See also Don Albert photos under Photographs.
    - American Songs, 1 folder (Box 181)
    - Archives, 1 folder (Box 180)
      Georgia State University (Mercer); Hamilton Jazz Archive; Rutgers Institute of Jazz Studies; Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound; Tulane; Vincent Voice Library; WFMT (Armstrong); WUOM (University of Michigan)
    - Bass Players, 1 folder; 1 unlabeled microcassette [3M 543 Micro Dicating Cassette] (Box 181)
    - Blues, 1 folder (Box 181)
    - Boogie Woogie, 3 folders (Box 181)
    - Books, 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Broadway Jazz, 1 folder (Box 182)
    - Burgundy Street, 1 folder (Box 182)
    - Clarinet, 1 folder (Box 182)
    - Gennett Records, 1 folder (Box 182)
    - Guitar, 1 folder (Box 182)
    - Harlem / 52nd Street / Lennox Avenue, 4 folders (Box 183)
    - Hefner, Hugh, 1 folder (Box 183)
    - Hot Bands of the 20s / Bix, 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Jazz Birthdays, 1 folder (Box 188)
    - Jazz History, 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Jazz Musicians - New Wave, 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Kelley, Peck / Jack Teagarden / Gospel Hymns and Spirituals [RWJ Research 2001], 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Lyrics binder, 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Miscellaneous, 1 folder (Box 180)
    - Prohibition, 1 folder (Box 183)
    - Saxophone, 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Showboat, 1 folder (Box 184)
    - Hal Smith Articles, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (data disc) (Box 180)
    - Spirituals, Hymns and The Blues, 1 folder (Box 184)
    - Swing [Revival], 1 folder (Box 184)
    - Texas Roots, 1 folder (Box 184)
    - Trombone, 1 folder (Box 184)
    - Trumpet, 1 folder (Box 184)
    - Tulane Oral History Transcripts: Johnny Wiggs, Nick La Rocca, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Tune Research. Armstrong 2001; Tunes 1921-1930; RW Tune List, 3 folders (Box 180)
  - Research files - people
    Musician and composer background files. Overlaps with artist/talent bios, but many were never featured in programs. Contains annotated photocopies (articles, book chapters, liner notes, sheet music), clippings, reviews, printouts from web, transcriptions, etc. Few are primary sources, and some are only one article about the subject. There is also correspondence about the programs.
    - Arlen, Harold, 3 folders (Box 172)
    - Armstrong, Louis, 8 folders (Box 172)
    - Avakian, George, 1 folder (Box 172)
    - Bailey, Pearl, 1 folder (Box 172)
    - Barker, Danny, 6 folders (Box 172)
    - Basie, Count, 1 folder (Box 173)
    - Bechet, Sidney, 1 folder (Box 173)
    - Beiderbecke, Bix, 4 folders (Box 173)
    - Burns, Ken, 1 folder (Box 173)
    - Caceres, Emilio and Ernie, 1 folder (Box 173)
    - Carter, Benny, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Cheatham, Doc, 1 folder (Box 173)
    - Clark, Garner, 1 folder (Box 173)
    - Coleman, Bill, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Condon, Eddie, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Cook, Will Marion, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - Crosby, Bing, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Crosby, Bob, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Darensbourg, Joe, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Davison, Wild Bill, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Dodds, Baby, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Donaldson, Walter, 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Edison, Harry "Sweets", 1 folder (Box 174)
    - Ellington, Duke, 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Fields, Dorothy, 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Fitzgerald, Ella, 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Fred and Ginger [Fred Astaire and Ginger Rogers], 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Gershwin, 3 folders (Box 182)
    - Gillespie, Dizzy, 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Goldkette, Jean, 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Goodman, Benny, 1 folder (Box 175)
    - Handy, W.C., 5 folders (Box 175)
    - Hays, Lee, 1 folder (Box 176)
    - Hodges, Johnny, 1 folder (Box 176)
    - Hill, Alex, 1 folder (Box 176)
    - Hines, Earl, 1 folder (Box 176)
    - Holiday, Billie, 2 folders (Box 176)
    - Johnson, Bunk, 1 folder (Box 176)
    - Johnson, James P., 2 folders (Box 176)
    - Kelly, Peck, 2 folders (Box 176)
    - Kern, Jerome, 1 folder (Box 176)
    - Krupa, Gene, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - La Rocca, Nick, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Lee, Peggy, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Malone, Stranger, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Mercer, Johnny, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Mezzrow, Mezz, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Moore, Freddie, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Morton, Jelly Roll, 4 folders (Box 177)
    - Murphy, Turk, 1 folder (Box 177)
    - Murrow, Edward R., 1 folder (Box 177)
    - New Orleans Rhythm Kings, 1 folder (Box 183)
    - Oliver, King, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Ory, Kid, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Page, Hot Lips, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Parker, Charlie, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Porter, Cole, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Rainey, Ma, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Razaf, Andy, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Reinhardt, Django, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Rollini, Adrian, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Runyan, Damon, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Shaw, Artie, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Smith, Bessie, 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Smith, Willie "The Lion", 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Spanier, Muggsy, 1 folder (Box 178)
    - Sullivan, Maxine, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Vaughan, Sarah, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Venuti, Joe, 2 folders (Box 179)
    - Waller, Fats, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Warren, Harry, 3 folders (Box 179)
    - Waters, Ethel, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Watters, Lu, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Wiley, Lee, 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Wilson, John S., 1 folder (Box 179)
    - Yerba Buena Stompers, 1 folder; 1 CD-R (Box 184)
  - Riverwalk library listing, 2012; 1 folder (Box 263)
    Bibliography of reference materials. All are now incorporated into the Stanford University Libraries general holdings.
- Program research recordings
  Historical music and interviews used for reference and in the production of programs, arranged alphabetically by principle subject. Much of the material comes from private collections, other archives, and commercial issues on 78 and LP. There are also some original interviews conducted by show host David Holt. Some of this material was also offered as supplemental material on the Riverwalk website. Many of the CD-Rs are from two binders titled "Interviews, Soundbites, etc." and from one binder titled "Interviews and Voicetracks 2006-2011." See also biographical files, program research files and program concept files.
  - Don Albert
    Albert, Don